{
    "math": [
      {
        "id": 1,
        "problem": "5 + 3",
        "solution": 8
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "problem": "9 - 4",
        "solution": 5
      },
      {
        "id": 3,
        "problem": "7 * 2",
        "solution": 14
      },
      {
        "id": 4,
        "problem": "12 / 4",
        "solution": 3
      },
      {
        "id": 5,
        "problem": "15 + 10",
        "solution": 25
      },
      {
        "id": 6,
        "problem": "18 - 9",
        "solution": 9
      },
      {
        "id": 7,
        "problem": "3 * 6",
        "solution": 18
      },
      {
        "id": 8,
        "problem": "16 / 2",
        "solution": 8
      },
      {
        "id": 9,
        "problem": "25 + 5",
        "solution": 30
      },
      {
        "id": 10,
        "problem": "30 - 15",
        "solution": 15
      }
    ]
  }
  